<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?> 
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="project-plan-render.xsl"?>
<p:plan plan-format="1.0" xmlns:p="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="Sisu">
  <p:release projectid="technology.sisu" version="0.1.0" />

  <p:introduction>
    <p>
      The Sisu project provides a dynamic dependency injection framework that can interact with OSGi services and Eclipse extensions.
    </p>
  </p:introduction>

  <p:release_deliverables>
    <p>
      The initial contribution is currently being prepared.
    </p>
  </p:release_deliverables>

  <p:release_milestones>
    <p:preamble>
      <p>
        Release milestones will be published as committer time allows.
      </p>
    </p:preamble>
    <p:milestone date="??/12/2012" milestone="M1">
      <div>0.1.0.M1</div>
    </p:milestone>
  </p:release_milestones>

  <p:target_environments>
    <p>
      Sisu consists of pure Java code and is expected to run on any JVM that supports Java SE 5 or newer.
    </p>
    <p:internationalization>
      <p>
        None of the Sisu deliverables are internationalized, any log and exception messages use English.
      </p>
    </p:internationalization>
  </p:target_environments>

  <p:compatibility_with_previous_releases>
    <h3>Compatibility with Sonatype Sisu</h3>
    <p>
      <strong>API Contract Compatibility:</strong>
      To comply with Eclipse Foundation requirements, all Sisu Java types/packages will be
      moved into the
      <code>org.eclipse.sisu</code>
      namespace. An external compatibility layer is being considered for users of Sonatype Sisu.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>Source Compatibility:</strong>
      To comply with Eclipse Foundation requirements, all Sisu Java types/packages will be
      moved into the
      <code>org.eclipse.sisu</code>
      namespace. While the API will undergo some refactoring and cleanup during the move to Eclipse, it is
      expected that
      typical clients mainly need to update their imports and make minor code changes to successfully build against the
      new Sisu API.
    </p>
  </p:compatibility_with_previous_releases>

  <p:themes_and_priorities>
    <p:preamble>
    </p:preamble>
    <p:theme name="Clean up API">
      <p:description>
        <p>
          With the move of the code into the
          <code>org.eclipse.sisu</code>
          namespace being a breaking change anyways, this provided an opportunity to remove deprecated code.
          Additionally, the API has been refactored in some places to ease future evolution and to improve its
          usability.
        </p>
      </p:description>
    </p:theme>
  </p:themes_and_priorities>

  <p:appendix />

</p:plan>